Never make the weapon the target
Anna is a action, adventure, thriller film directed by Luc Besson.
Beneath Anna Poliatova's striking beauty lies a secret that will unleash her indelible
strength and skill to become one of the world's most feared government assassins.
Anna, played by Sasha Luss.
Olga, played by Helen Mirren.
Alex Tchenkov, played by Luke Evans.
Lenny Miller, played by Cillian Murphy.
Maude, played by Lera Abova.
Piotr, played by Alexander Petrov.
Anna (stylized as ANИA) is a 2019 action thriller film
written, produced and directed by Luc Besson.
The film stars Sasha Luss as the eponymous assassin, alongside Luke
Evans, Cillian Murphy, Helen Mirren, and Alexander Petrov.
The French production was theatrically released in the United States on 21 June 2019 by
Summit Entertainment and on 10 July 2019 by Pathé Distribution in France.
It received mixed reviews from critics and grossed $31
million worldwide against a $30 million budget.
The film explores themes of central intelligence agency (cia),
paris, france, cold war, kgb, female assassin.
The tone is intense.